The most important part of a story is the ending.
Secret Window is a mystery, thriller film directed by David Koepp.
Mort Rainey, a writer just emerging from a painful divorce with his ex-wife, is stalked at his remote lake
house by a psychotic stranger and would-be scribe who claims Rainey swiped his best story idea.
But as Rainey endeavors to prove his innocence, he
begins to question his own sanity.
Mort Rainey, played by Johnny Depp.
John Shooter, played by John Turturro.
Amy Rainey, played by Maria Bello.
Ted Milner, played by Timothy Hutton.
Ken Karsch, played by Charles S. Dutton.
Sheriff Dave Newsome, played by Len Cariou.
Secret Window is a 2004 American thriller film
starring Johnny Depp and John Turturro.
It was written and directed by David Koepp, based on the novella Secret Window, Secret Garden
by Stephen King, featuring a musical score by Philip Glass and Geoff Zanelli.
The story appeared in King's 1990 collection Four Past Midnight and follows a struggling writer who is terrorized by an
elusive adversary while dealing with an ongoing divorce from his estranged wife and tolerating her new husband.
The film was released on March 12, 2004, by Columbia Pictures; it was a
moderate box office success and received mixed reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of adultery, jealousy, nightmare, police, isolation.
The tone is intense and mind_bending.